ashtag
Wars as I mentioned earlier Sunday is
Mother's Day so in honor of Mom's
everywhere tonight's hashtag is Mom
songs so examples would be Don't Stop
Till You Get Enough
vegetables I can drive
55 jump jump but not on the
couch uh I'm going to put 60 seconds on
the clock and go Lauren you don't know
how it feels to be the only one who
cleans up around here that's bu oh the
guilt yes Matt besser carry on my
wayward son but be home by nine yes
pun Matt fesser again uh no rough
housing on The Stairway to Heaven points
points Rich vure sucker Mommy
adeas Points Lauren who let the dogs out
somebody please tell me points yeah
Bridge everybody has visitation on the
weekend
yes divorce mom yes
yes that enter the sandman not in my
house take off your
shoes Rich lunchbox
[Laughter]
fever no one else is going to remember
Cat Scratch Fever other than the two of
us rich what r s p c your mother
Bridge blurred C-section
lines
what that's a good
[Applause]
one